<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Library Application</string>
    <string name="title_activity_scrolling">ScrollingActivity</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        "Material is the metaphor.\n\n"

        "A material metaphor is the unifying theory of a rationalized space and a system of motion."
        "The material is grounded in tactile reality, inspired by the study of paper and ink, yet "
        "technologically advanced and open to imagination and magic.\n"
        "Surfaces and edges of the material provide visual cues that are grounded in reality. The "
        "use of familiar tactile attributes helps users quickly understand affordances. Yet the "
        "flexibility of the material creates new affordances that supercede those in the physical "
        "world, without breaking the rules of physics.\n"
        "The fundamentals of light, surface, and movement are key to conveying how objects move, "
        "interact, and exist in space and in relation to each other. Realistic lighting shows "
        "seams, divides space, and indicates moving parts.\n\n"

        "Bold, graphic, intentional.\n\n"

        "The foundational elements of print based design typography, grids, space, scale, color, "
        "and use of imagery guide visual treatments. These elements do far more than please the "
        "eye. They create hierarchy, meaning, and focus. Deliberate color choices, edge to edge "
        "imagery, large scale typography, and intentional white space create a bold and graphic "
        "interface that immerse the user in the experience.\n"
        "An emphasis on user actions makes core functionality immediately apparent and provides "
        "waypoints for the user.\n\n"

        "Motion provides meaning.\n\n"

        "Motion respects and reinforces the user as the prime mover. Primary user actions are "
        "inflection points that initiate motion, transforming the whole design.\n"
        "All action takes place in a single environment. Objects are presented to the user without "
        "breaking the continuity of experience even as they transform and reorganize.\n"
        "Motion is meaningful and appropriate, serving to focus attention and maintain continuity. "
        "Feedback is subtle yet clear. Transitions are efﬁcient yet coherent.\n\n"

        "3D world.\n\n"

        "The material environment is a 3D space, which means all objects have x, y, and z "
        "dimensions. The z-axis is perpendicularly aligned to the plane of the display, with the "
        "positive z-axis extending towards the viewer. Every sheet of material occupies a single "
        "position along the z-axis and has a standard 1dp thickness.\n"
        "On the web, the z-axis is used for layering and not for perspective. The 3D world is "
        "emulated by manipulating the y-axis.\n\n"

        "Light and shadow.\n\n"

        "Within the material environment, virtual lights illuminate the scene. Key lights create "
        "directional shadows, while ambient light creates soft shadows from all angles.\n"
        "Shadows in the material environment are cast by these two light sources. In Android "
        "development, shadows occur when light sources are blocked by sheets of material at "
        "various positions along the z-axis. On the web, shadows are depicted by manipulating the "
        "y-axis only. The following example shows the card with a height of 6dp.\n\n"

        "Resting elevation.\n\n"

        "All material objects, regardless of size, have a resting elevation, or default elevation "
        "that does not change. If an object changes elevation, it should return to its resting "
        "elevation as soon as possible.\n\n"

        "Component elevations.\n\n"

        "The resting elevation for a component type is consistent across apps (e.g., FAB elevation "
        "does not vary from 6dp in one app to 16dp in another app).\n"
        "Components may have different resting elevations across platforms, depending on the depth "
        "of the environment (e.g., TV has a greater depth than mobile or desktop).\n\n"

        "Responsive elevation and dynamic elevation offsets.\n\n"

        "Some component types have responsive elevation, meaning they change elevation in response "
        "to user input (e.g., normal, focused, and pressed) or system events. These elevation "
        "changes are consistently implemented using dynamic elevation offsets.\n"
        "Dynamic elevation offsets are the goal elevation that a component moves towards, relative "
        "to the component’s resting state. They ensure that elevation changes are consistent "
        "across actions and component types. For example, all components that lift on press have "
        "the same elevation change relative to their resting elevation.\n"
        "Once the input event is completed or cancelled, the component will return to its resting "
        "elevation.\n\n"

        "Avoiding elevation interference.\n\n"

        "Components with responsive elevations may encounter other components as they move between "
        "their resting elevations and dynamic elevation offsets. Because material cannot pass "
        "through other material, components avoid interfering with one another any number of ways, "
        "whether on a per component basis or using the entire app layout.\n"
        "On a component level, components can move or be removed before they cause interference. "
        "For example, a floating action button (FAB) can disappear or move off screen before a "
        "user picks up a card, or it can move if a snackbar appears.\n"
        "On the layout level, design your app layout to minimize opportunities for interference. "
        "For example, position the FAB to one side of stream of a cards so the FAB won’t interfere "
        "when a user tries to pick up one of cards.\n\n"
    </string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_dashboard">DashboardActivity</string>
    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="first_fragment_label">First Fragment</string>
    <string name="second_fragment_label">Second Fragment</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>

    <string name="hello_first_fragment">Hello first fragment</string>
    <string name="hello_second_fragment">Hello second fragment. Arg: %1$s</string>

    <string-array name="genres">
        <item>All</item>
        <item>Fiction</item>
        <item>Drama</item>
        <item>Novel</item>
        <item>Detective</item>
        <item>Historical</item>
        <item>Fantasy</item>
        <item>Poetry</item>
        <item>Spiritual</item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="books">
        <item>And Still I Rise</item>
        <item>Call Us What We Carry</item>
        <item>Catching Fire</item>
        <item>Forty days of Musa Dagh</item>
        <item>Hamlet</item>
        <item>Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince</item>
        <item>Jane Eyre</item>
        <item>Me Before You</item>
        <item>Mere Christianity</item>
        <item>Murder of Roger Ackroyd</item>
        <item>Romeo and Juliet</item>
        <item>Samvel</item>
        <item>The Alchemist</item>
        <item>The Big Sleep</item>
        <item>The Book of Friday</item>
        <item>The Book of Sadness</item>
        <item>The Book Thief</item>
        <item>The Fault In Our Stars</item>
        <item>The Great Gatsby</item>
        <item>The Hound of the Baskervilles</item>
        <item>The Hunger Games</item>
        <item>The Sun and Her Flowers</item>
        <item>Vardanank</item>
        <item>1984</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="pages">
        <item>64</item>
        <item>240</item>
        <item>391</item>
        <item>893</item>
        <item>104</item>
        <item>672</item>
        <item>536</item>
        <item>480</item>
        <item>256</item>
        <item>312</item>
        <item>156</item>
        <item>480</item>
        <item>218</item>
        <item>277</item>
        <item>124</item>
        <item>620</item>
        <item>552</item>
        <item>313</item>
        <item>208</item>
        <item>174</item>
        <item>384</item>
        <item>256</item>
        <item>918</item>
        <item>328</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="authors">
        <item>Maya Angelou</item>
        <item>Amanda Gorman</item>
        <item>Suzanne Collins</item>
        <item>Franz Werfel</item>
        <item>William Shakespeare</item>
        <item>J.K.Rowling</item>
        <item>Charlotte Bronte</item>
        <item>Jojo Moyes</item>
        <item>C.S.Lewis</item>
        <item>Agatha Christie</item>
        <item>William Shakespeare</item>
        <item>Raffi</item>
        <item>Paulo Coelho</item>
        <item>Raymond Chandler</item>
        <item>Hakob Meghapart</item>
        <item>Grigor of Narek</item>
        <item>Markus Zusak</item>
        <item>John Green</item>
        <item>F.Scott Fitzgerald</item>
        <item>Arthur Conan Doyle</item>
        <item>Suzanne Collins</item>
        <item>Rapi Kaur</item>
        <item>Derenik Demirchian</item>
        <item>George Orwell</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="descriptions">

        <item>The book is primarily about self-respect and confidence. In the poem, Angelou reveals how she will overcome anything through her
self-esteem. She shows how nothing can get her down. She will rise to any occasion, and nothing, not even her skin color, will hold her back.</item>

        <item>In Call Us What We Carry, Gorman explores history, language, identity, and erasure through an imaginative and intimate
collage. Harnessing the collective grief of a global pandemic, this beautifully designed volume features poems in many inventive styles
and structures and shines a light on a moment of reckoning.</item>

        <item>After arriving safely home from their unprecedented victory in the 74th Annual Hunger Games, Katniss Everdeen
and Peeta Mellark discover that they must do a quick turnaround and begin a Victors Tour. As she and Peeta travel throughout
the districts, Katniss senses a rebellion is stirring. However, President Snow proves that he is still very
much in control when word comes of a cruel change in the rules for the upcoming 75th Hunger Games.</item>

        <item>The novel tells the true story of several embattled Armenian villages whose inhabitants refused to obey deportation orders
in 1915 and took up arms in self-defense, holding out for, in fact, more than the biblically resonant 40 days of the novel’s title. Many
survived and were rescued by the French Navy.</item>

        <item>The ghost of the King of Denmark tells his son Hamlet to avenge his murder by killing the new king, Hamlets uncle. Hamlet feigns madness,
contemplates life and death, and seeks revenge. His uncle, fearing for his life, also devises plots to kill Hamlet.</item>

        <item>The war against Voldemort is not going well. Dumbledore is absent from Hogwarts for long stretches of time.
As in all wars, life goes on. Sixth-year students learn to Apparate. The classes are tough, though Harry receives some help from the
mysterious Half-Blood Prince. And all the while Harry searches for the full story of the boy who became Voldemort-hoping to find what
may be his only vulnerability.</item>

        <item>The novel follows the story of Jane, a seemingly plain and simple girl as she battles through lifes struggles. Jane has many
obstacles in her life - her cruel and abusive Aunt Reed, the grim conditions at Lowood school, her love for Rochester and Rochesters marriage
to Bertha.</item>

        <item>It is about a woman, Louisa, who is desperate for a job and accepts a position as private caregiver to a young disabled man, a quadriplegic, from a
wealthy family. This man, Will Traynor, had once been on the fast track in life — a high powered business man who pursued a thrilling life of action and adventure.</item>

        <item>Lewis aims to prove to the sensible skeptic that God does exist and that He sent His son Jesus Christ to redeem the world. The book begins with
a logical proof for the Christian God and then transitions into a discussion of the common ground upon which all of those of the Christian faith stand together.</item>

        <item>Dr. James Sheppard, lives with his older unmarried sister Caroline in the country village of King’s Abbot on the outskirts
of London. As the local physician with an active practice, Dr. Sheppard becomes emmeshed in a mysterious suicide and murder and the ensuing
investigations into them over a nine-day period after the death of Roger Ackroyd. Detective Poirot, despite having decided to retire, takes
the responsibility of finding out who killed Roger Ackroyd.</item>

        <item>It is a tragic love story where the two main characters, Romeo and Juliet, are supposed to be sworn enemies but fall in love. Due to their families ongoing
conflict, they cannot be together, so they kill themselves because they cannot cope with being separated from one another.</item>

        <item>The novel tells the story of a young nobleman Samvel. His father betrayed his motherland. Now Samvel, as well as all his family, has to make
a choice between his country and father. The novel beautifully describes the abundance of love, loyalty and the reality of war in Armenia in 370s.</item>

        <item>The Alchemist is a classic novel in which a boy named Santiago embarks on a journey seeking treasure in the Egyptian pyramids after having a recurring
dream about it and on the way meets mentors, falls in love, and most importantly, learns the true importance of who he is and how to improve himself.</item>

        <item>Private investigator Philip Marlowe is hired by wealthy General Sternwood to stop a blackmailer. Marlowe suspects that the old General
is merely testing his caliber before trusting him with a bigger job, one involving Sternwoods two amoral daughters.</item>

        <item>The Book of Friday, or Urbatagirk in Armenian, was the first printed book in the Armenian language. Its content was partly religious, partly
secular, consisting of cures and prayers for the sick, ancient writings, myths, long quotations from The Book of Sadness (or  The Book of Lamentations) by
Gregory of Narek, the Prayer of Cyprianos of Antioch, the story of the Virgin and Justinian, et cetera.</item>

        <item>The Book of Sadness is a poem written by saint Gregory of Narek in 1002. The poem consists of over eleven thousand lines of prayer. It was
originally written in Ancient Armenian or Grabar. It has been translated to several languages, including English, Russian and Farsi.</item>

        <item>The Book Thief tells the story of Liesel, a little girl who is taken to a new home because her mother cannot afford
to take care of her. The story is told by Death, who becomes a character you come to respect and even feel sorry for by the end.</item>

        <item>Despite the tumor-shrinking medical miracle that has bought her a few years, Hazel has never been anything but terminal, her
final chapter inscribed upon diagnosis. But when a gorgeous plot twist named Augustus Waters suddenly appears at Cancer Kid Support Group,
Hazels story is about to be completely rewritten.</item>

        <item>The story is narrated by a World War I veteran Nick Carraway, who, after moving to Long Island becomes the neighbor of some
millionaire named Jay Gatsby. The story tells us about Gatsby, his past, his love towards Daisy Buchanan, who had reluctantly got married to
Tom Buchanan while Jay fought in the First World War. The book gives the reader details of Jay and Daisys love, Toms affair and how it
affected Gatsbys life.</item>

        <item>The Hound of the Baskervilles opens with a mini mystery—Sherlock Holmes and Dr. Watson speculate on the identity of the owner of a cane
that has been left in their office by an unknown visitor. Wowing Watson with his fabulous powers of observation, Holmes predicts the appearance of James
Mortimer, owner of the found object and a convenient entrée into the baffling curse of the Baskervilles.</item>

        <item>In what was once North America, the Capitol of Panem maintains its hold on its 12 districts by forcing them
each to select a boy and a girl, called Tributes, to compete in a nationally televised event called the Hunger Games. Every
citizen must watch as the youths fight to the death until only one remains. District 12 Tribute Katniss Everdeen has little
to rely on, other than her hunting skills and sharp instincts, in an arena where she must weigh survival against love.</item>

        <item>A vibrant and transcendent journey about growth and healing. Ancestry and honoring ones roots. Expatriation and rising up to find
a home within yourself. Divided into five chapters and illustrated by kaur, the sun and her flowers is a journey of wilting, falling, rooting,
rising, and blooming.</item>

        <item>This historical novel tells the story of the Armenian-Persian war in 451, which is as well knwon as the War of Vardans or the Vardanank War.
It tells the story of the first war for Christianity taking place on the soil of the first Christian state. The novel describes the struggle of keeping the
faith that the Armenians went through.</item>

        <item>In George Orwells 1984, Winston Smith wrestles with oppression in Oceania, a place where the Party scrutinizes human actions with
ever-watchful Big Brother. Defying a ban on individuality, Winston dares to express his thoughts in a diary and pursues a relationship with Julia.</item>

    </string-array>
</resources>